(Official:)Is that the song
from Toy Story?
(Penny:)He loves that movie.
(voice breaking):
I do.
(Bernadette:)Aw, that was beautiful.
Yeah.
(Howard:)I mean, not like our
wedding beautiful.
(Bernadette:)No, we totally won.
(Sheldon:)Amy, I don't understand,
are we broken up or not?
(Sheldon:)It's like you can't
make up your mind.
(Amy:)It's because you're not
giving me any space to think.
(Sheldon:)Well, you should think fast,
(Sheldon:)because men can sire offspring
their entire lives,
(Sheldon:)but those eggs you're toting
around have a sell-by date.
(Amy:)You know what, Sheldon,
you've made this really easy.
(Amy:)You're immature, you're selfish,
you just insulted me to my face.
(Amy:)I don't need any more time
to think. We're broken up.
(Sheldon:)Amy...
(Sheldon:)Will someone take me home?
(Raj:)Yeah. Come on,
I'll give you a ride.
MINISTER:
...symbolizes your eternal love.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
We did it!
(Leonard:)I'm so glad
you guys could watch!